{
    "subject": "resource/Christian_Berkel",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Berlin",
    "human_readable": "Christian Berkel was born in Berlin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8678213953971863,
            "question": "Where was Christian Berkel born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6349949240684509,
            "question": "Is Christian Berkel German?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6097056865692139,
            "question": "In what city did Christian Berkel grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48221078515052795,
            "question": "What is Christian Berkel known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2946169078350067,
            "question": "Is Christian Berkel still acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19543524086475372,
            "question": "Has Christian Berkel won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19223549962043762,
            "question": "Who are some of Christian Berkel's famous co-stars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18090271949768066,
            "question": "Does Christian Berkel have any other notable accomplishments besides acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1557757407426834,
            "question": "What is one of Christian Berkel's most popular roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1346302479505539,
            "question": "What kind of movies has Christian Berkel starred in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Christian Berkel was born in Berlin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4227_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is one of Christian Berkel's most popular roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4227_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Christian Berkel have any other notable accomplishments besides acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4227_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Christian Berkel's famous co-stars?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4227_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4227_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that the statement \"Christian Berkel was born in Berlin\" is supported by multiple documents. Here's the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information that multiple documents state Christian Berkel was born in Berlin, Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}